cosme-de.com 2018-05-24

# COSME-DE.COM | Shop for skincare & cosmetics products, Be the Beautiful One

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING COSME-DE.COM ("Site") OR YOU MAY BECOME A MEMBER OF COSME-DE.COM. COSME-DE.COM PROVIDES ITS SERVICE TO YOU SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING POLICY.**

Last updated on November 25, 2015. 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**ACCEPTANCE OF THIS POLICY**

At COSME-DE.COM, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Your understanding and compliance with COSME-DE.COM's Privacy Policy will help us provide you with an efficient and satisfying shopping experience. Our Privacy Policy covers any personal information that COSME-DE.COM obtains from you when you use the services provided on COSME-DE.COM. 

By using the services provided on COSME-DE.COM, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy, including our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so we encourage you to check back periodically to see if we have made any changes. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Depending on how you use COSME-DE.COM, we may ask you to share personally identifiable information with us to provide our services, and to administer our business. 

  * **When browsing at COSME-DE.COM**  
COSME-DE.COM use "cookies" to collect non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address, browser type, domain name, and the specific COSME-DE.COM pages that you visit. 

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to track your preferences and purchases as you navigate through our website and to save you from having to re-enter information every time you visit COSME-DE.COM. By using cookies to track your visits, we can make your next shopping experience at COSME-DE.COM better. 

To search our website and/or place an order on COSME-DE.COM, you need to have the cookies feature of your web browser turned on. Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookies by deleting them, blocking them, or alerting you when a cookie file is stored. Please review your browser's instructions on these functions. If you choose to disable the cookies feature of your web browser, you may not be able to place an order or otherwise use some or all of the features provided at COSME-DE.COM. 

  * **When registering at COSME-DE.COM**   
COSME-DE.COM asks you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your full name and email address. We may also ask you to provide birthday information, favorite brand(s), skin type and Newsletter subscription preference to us on a voluntary basis. Collecting this information allows us to enhance your overall shopping experience - a more personalized experience. 

You can also subscribe for Newsletter updates alone without prior register by providing your email address through our site services. 

  * **When ordering at COSME-DE.COM**   
COSME-DE.COM asks you to provide personally identifiable information to us when you place an order with COSME-DE.COM. We ask for your email address, shipping address and phone number of the shipping destination, your billing address, your credit card number, and your credit card expiration date. Collecting this information allows us to complete your order efficiently, to notify you of your order status, to provide personalized interaction, and to use for marketing purposes if needed. 
  * **When contacting COSME-DE.COM**   
COSME-DE.COM asks you to provide personally identifiable information to us when you contacting us. We ask for your name, email address, your located country/region and phone number. Collecting this information allows us to provide you a more personalized assistance from our customer care department. 

**INFORMATION USAGE**

The information we collect on COSME-DE.COM may be used to fulfill your requests (such as product orders and responses to email questions) and to communicate with you about your membership, order or product offers and promotions. 

We may use the information collected at COSME-DE.COM for our internal operations. Such entities may receive personally identifiable information to allow them to perform their duties, but they may not use that information for any other purpose. 

**INFOMRATION DISCLOSURE & SHARING**

We do not share, sell, trade, or rent all your personally identifiable information to third parties for their marketing purpose without your explicit consent. All personally identifiable information held by the COSME-DE.COM will be kept confidential but we may, where such disclosure is necessary to satisfy the purpose, or a directly related purpose, for which the information was collected provide such information to the following parties: 

  * We may disclose the information we collect about you (including personally identifiable information) to third parties to comply with applicable laws, regulations, and/or governmental requests. 
  * We may also disclose such information to verify or enforce compliance with our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, to process and fill your order, reduce credit risk, protect against fraud, protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the COSME-DE.COM, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure. 
  * Certain services or customer surveys might require support by third party (such as agents, technical services provider, transportation companies, mailing companies, prizes processing companies, etc.). In order to provide such services or surveys to you, the site is necessary to share your personal information with that partner. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * In some instances, we may share non-personally identifying information collected on COSME-DE.COM with third parties for statistics and web traffic auditing purpose. 

**INFORMATION SERCURITY**

COSME-DE.COM works to protect your personal information and credit card detail when you shop with us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology - the industry standard - to encrypt the personal information and credit card detail you provide during the order process. 

To ensure the security of your personal information, you should always provide that information over a secure connection. You can check the existence of a secure connection by referring to the URL in your web browser. Whenever you are connected to a secure server, that connection will be represented in the URL as "https://..." rather than "http://...". And you see a highlighted and closed lock. 

We urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your COSME-DE.COM password with anyone or in any unsolicited phone call or email. 

COSME-DE.COM strives to ensure the integrity and security of its network and systems. There may be violations logging processes for investigation of any unauthorized attempt to access information. 

**MODIFY YOUR INFORMATION & OPTING OUT**

You can access and modify the personally identifiable information you provide us and choose not to receive email promotions, new products updates from us. Simply login My Account in the top menu of each page on our website at any time. 

You may also Contact COSME-DE.COM with a message requesting that you wish to cancel your membership with us. 

**HOW TO UNSUBSCRIBE FROM RECEIVING EMAIL PROMOTIONS AND PRODUCT UPDATES**

If you would like to unsubscribe from our email communications, simply click on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom in any COSME-DE.COM promotional emails or product update emails you receive. If you are unsure of how to unsubscribe, please contact us. 

**ABOUT CONTACT DETAILS**

Your personal information have been collected during account registration and payment process. If you have any questions about the privacy and security of your personal information, such as accessing, correcting, updating or removing your personal information, or if you have a complaint about the breach of your information privacy, please feel free to contact us. 

COSME-DE.COM  
12/F, Yau Lee Centre,  
45 Hoi Yuen Road, Kwun Tong,  
Kowloon, Hong Kong 

Email: [email protected]

Tel: (852) 3557-6150
